This just in:
New evidence that
这只是在：
新证据表明
unidentified flying objects
have been secretly visiting
不明飞行物
曾秘密拜访过
Bikini Bottom for years.
多年来比基尼泳裤。
General, what are the
chances that these photos
一般情况下，有哪些
有可能这些照片
and videos are just a hoax?
视频只是一个骗局？
99.99999%.
99.99999%。
There you have it--
给你了--
conclusive proof that
there is a 0.00001% chance
确凿的证据表明
有 0.00001% 的机会
UFOs are real.
UFO 是真实存在的。
That means there could be
evidence of UFOs anywhere!
这意味着可能有
任何地方都有不明飞行物的证据！
Let's go find some.
我们去找一些吧。
Here, alien.
在这里，外星人。
Alien! Alien!
外星人！外星人！
- Hmm.
- Huh?
- 唔。
- 啊？
Uh, huh?
呃，嗯？
Huh?
啊？
It's the middle of the night!
已经是半夜了！
What are you two idiots doing?
你们两个白痴在做什么？
We found an
alien crop circle!
我们发现了一个
外星麦田怪圈！
It's only a crop circle
because you're
这只是一个麦田圈
因为你是
stomping on my begonias!
踩我的海棠！
Huh?
啊？
Okay.
好的。
Yeah, that is us.
是的，那就是我们。
We're hunting space
aliens and UFOs.
我们正在寻找空间
外星人和不明飞行物。
Space aliens and UFOs
do not exist.
太空外星人和不明飞行物
不存在。
Go to sleep!
睡觉！
Okay.
好的。
You want to see space aliens?
你想看太空外星人吗？
I'll show you space aliens.
我将向你展示太空外星人。
This could
definitely be a UFO.
这可以
肯定是不明飞行物。
A real UFO!
真正的不明飞行物！
both: First contact!
双方：第一次接触！
First contact!
第一次接触！
both: Whoa!
两人：哇！
Intergalactic.
星际。
Spacey.
史派西。
Cosmic.
宇宙的。
We just got hit
by a flying saucer!
我们刚刚被击中
通过飞碟！
- Yeah!
- Yeah! Cool!
- 是的！
- 是的！凉爽的！
Cool! Yeah!
凉爽的！是的！
Greetings, earthlings.
问候，地球人。
A r-r-real space alien.
一个真实的太空外星人。
Greetings, sir.
你好，先生。
It's me, you tinfoil twits.
是我，你们这群锡纸傻瓜。
It was all me.
都是我。
Space aliens don't exist.
太空外星人并不存在。
Got it?
知道了？
Thank you, Squidward.
谢谢你，章鱼哥。
We can see now how
silly we really were.
我们现在可以看到如何
我们真的很傻。
I know.
我知道。
Let's play superheroes instead.
让我们来扮演超级英雄吧。
Yeah!
是的！
At least we know they're real.
至少我们知道它们是真实的。
Idiots.
白痴。
At last, evidence of our
ancient aquatic ancestors.
最后，我们的证据
古代水生祖先。
We must take the artifact
back to the ship.
我们必须拿走神器
回到船上。
We'll be rich.
我们会变得富有。
Rich, I say.
富有，我说。
I told you two,
space aliens don't exist.
我告诉你们两个，
太空外星人并不存在。
Go away!
离开！
Oh, no.
哦，不。
The artifact is infested
with a parasite.
神器已被感染
有寄生虫。
We must eradicate it
before our departure.
我们必须消灭它
在我们出发之前。
I'm telling you,
it's always something.
我告诉你，
它总是有一些东西。
Huh?
啊？
Who--who's there?
谁——谁在那儿？
Ahh!
啊！
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
噢！噢！噢！噢！
Ah-ha!
啊哈！
My holes!
我的洞！
Oh, my holes!
哦，我的洞！
Thank Neptune
I have my readers.
评分此翻译： 感谢你的评分 不好 好
我有我的读者。
Have SpongeBob and Patrick
gone cuckoo?
有海绵宝宝和帕特里克
杜鹃走了吗？
You!
你！
SpongeBob and Patrick,
take off those stupid masks!
海绵宝宝和帕特里克，
摘掉那些愚蠢的面具！
I know it's you.
我知道是你。
Stop it.
停止吧。
You're hurting me.
你伤害了我。
Mayday!
劳动节！
We need backup.
我们需要备份。
Will you two
shut up in there?
你们两个愿意吗
关在那儿？
I'm trying to get your heads--
我正在努力让你明白——
off?
离开？
Those nimrods were right.
那些尼姆罗德是对的。
Aliens are real!
外星人是真实存在的！
SpongeBob, let me in!
海绵宝宝，让我进去！
You were right!
你是对的！
Tell Patrick you were right!
告诉帕特里克你是对的！
Success.
成功。
The vermin has evacuated.
害虫已经撤离。
Let's take the artifact
to our ship
来拿神器吧
到我们的船
before that horrible stinkbug
comes back.
在那个可怕的臭虫之前
回来了。
No! Wait! Wait!
不！等待！等待！
Wait, wait, wait!
等等，等等，等等！
Hmm.
唔。
So I says, I'll show
you a tractor beam.
所以我说，我会展示
你是牵引光束。
All right,
who's in charge here?
好吧，
这里谁负责？
I want to speak to the manager.
我想和经理谈谈。
Manager?
经理？
Take me to your leader.
带我去见你们的领导。
That would be our supervisor.
那将是我们的主管。
His office is down this hall.
他的办公室就在这个大厅下面。
You just make a left
then a right.
你只需向左转
然后是一个权利。
Don't talk to him.
别和他说话。
He is the vermin we eradicated.
他是我们消灭的害虫。
Looks like somebody
failed eradication class.
看起来像某人
消灭班失败。
Zip it.
拉上拉链。
I outrank you both.
我的级别比你们俩都高。
I want you to put my home
back where you found it.
我要你把我的家
回到你发现它的地方。
Could you step forward?
你能上前一步吗？
I'm hard of hearing.
我听力不好。
Sure.
当然。
And another thing.
还有一件事。
What's the big idea
of coming to my planet
有什么大创意
来到我的星球
and taking my house
out of my yard
并夺走我的房子
从我的院子里出来
just because it looked
like your stupid head?
只是因为它看起来
喜欢你的傻脑袋吗？
Talking vermin are
the worst kind.
会说话的害虫是
最糟糕的一种。
Am I right?
我说得对吗？
Just so it's not
a total loss,
只是这样才不是
完全损失，
I say we run some tests
and do a probe.
我说我们进行一些测试
并进行探测。
Hooray!
We're doing a probe!
万岁！
我们正在进行调查！
all: Probe! Probe! Probe!
全体：探测！探测！探测！
Probe! Probe! Probe!
探测！探测！探测！
Probe! Probe!
- Probe?
探测！探测！
- 探测？
Probe! Probe! Probe!
探测！探测！探测！
Probe! Probe!
探测！探测！
X-ray.
X 射线。
Despite the large cranium,
尽管颅骨很大，
the brain seems
below average size.
大脑似乎
低于平均尺寸。
Hey!
嘿！
High blood pressure.
高血压。
Better watch that temper.
最好注意一下脾气。
Rotate neck.
旋转脖子。
Nose hose.
鼻管。
Impressive storage space.
令人印象深刻的存储空间。
Now for the fun part.
现在是有趣的部分。
Ahh!
啊！
Freedom!
自由！
all: Hut. Hut. Hut. Hut. Hut.
全体：小屋。小屋。小屋。小屋。小屋。
Hut. Hut. Hut. Hut. Hut.
小屋。小屋。小屋。小屋。小屋。
Huh?
啊？
Daddy.
爸爸。
Huh?
啊？
No!
不！
Please don't probe me!
请不要试探我！
Huh?
啊？
In this probe,
I will be asking you
在本次探查中，
我会问你
embarrassing questions
about your childhood.
尴尬的问题
关于你的童年。
Well, I guess I did have
trouble making friends.
嗯，我想我确实有过
交朋友有困难。
Then when I was three,
I said, "Mumsy, I told you,
然后当我三岁的时候，
我说：“妈妈，我告诉过你，
I don't like kelp juice."
我不喜欢海带汁。”
And she said, "Well, I don't
like being called Mumsy."
她说：“好吧，我不
就像被称为妈妈一样。”
And then--
all: Enough!
然后——
全体：够了！
Good riddance, vermin.
祝你摆脱困境，害虫。
Keep your dumb, old artifact.
保留你那愚蠢的旧神器。
And you can keep your
mother stories too.
并且您可以保留您的
妈妈的故事也有。
Oy vey!
哎哟喂！
Squidward, if I
didn't know better,
章鱼哥，如果我
不知道更好，
I'd be thinking that was
a real alien spaceship.
我想那是
一艘真正的外星飞船。
But we do know better,
huh, Squidward?
但我们确实更清楚，
哈，章鱼哥？
I was wrong, okay?
我错了好吗？
Aliens are real!
外星人是真实存在的！
I was on their ship, and I was
telling them about my mother,
我在他们的船上，而且我
向他们讲述我的母亲，
and--and--and--and--
和——和——和——和——
We get it, Squidward.
我们明白了，章鱼哥。
Aliens don't exist!
外星人并不存在！
But they do exist.
但它们确实存在。
Of course.
当然。